<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="atom.xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://agency-fund.github.io/chatsel-docs/blog</id>
    <title>ChatSEL 🌱 Blog</title>
    <updated>2025-02-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://agency-fund.github.io/chatsel-docs/blog"/>
    <subtitle>ChatSEL 🌱 Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://agency-fund.github.io/chatsel-docs/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About Us]]></title>
        <id>https://agency-fund.github.io/chatsel-docs/blog/aboutus</id>
        <link href="https://agency-fund.github.io/chatsel-docs/blog/aboutus"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our team brings together deep domain expertise in psychology and behavioral science, as well as strong technical skills in software and data engineering working environments.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our team brings together deep domain expertise in psychology and behavioral science, as well as strong technical skills in software and data engineering working environments.</p>
<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="core-team">Core Team<a href="https://agency-fund.github.io/chatsel-docs/blog/aboutus#core-team" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Core Team" title="Direct link to Core Team">​</a></h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Zezhen Wu</strong> will lead the development of SEL content, research strategies, and product development. As a behavioral scientist at the Agency Fund with a PhD in Psychology and Social Intervention, Zezhen has extensive experience designing educational and psychological interventions in low- and middle-income countries.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Lucero Ramirez Varela</strong> is a doctoral student in the Psychology and Social Intervention Program at NYU Steinhardt. Lucero is passionate about understanding how high-quality evidence about developmental science can lead and promote action across multiple stakeholders. She also works on the content development of ChatSEL and leads the partnership with Enseña por Colombia to pilot ChatSEL in Colombian classrooms.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Edmund Korley</strong> is a software engineer at the Agency Fund with a decade of experience in the tech and social sectors. He has worked on diverse projects ranging from data extraction systems for police departments to financial lending tools and has substantial experience building LLM prototypes for NGOs. Edmund is passionate about using technology to promote global economic and social justice and plays an active role in driving AI adoption in Africa.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Linus Wong</strong> is a data and software engineer at the Agency Fund, specializing in A/B testing, dashboard building, and infrastructure monitoring. Linus brings expertise in tools such as Metabase, New Relic, Grafana, and Prometheus, and has strong experience in data science, ELT processes, and supporting A/B testing for multiple Agency Fund partners.</p>
</li>
</ul>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Zezhen (Michael) Wu</name>
            <uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/zezhenwu/</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Edmund Korley</name>
            <uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/edmundkorley/</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Wong</name>
            <uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/linus-wong-999b551/</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Lucero Ramirez Varela</name>
            <uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/luceroramirezvarela/?locale=en_US</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="introduction" term="introduction"/>
    </entry>
</feed>